T-R-A-R-I-A... T-R-A-R-I-A... Huh?
T-R-A-R-I-A... Heh heh heh.
What's up?
I'm not complaining.
But why stream at 11am?
Because I'm just quirky like that.
I felt like playing Terraria.
What can I say?
What are we drinking?
Uh, just a can of Coke.
The classic.
I'm not the classic Coke.
I mean, Coke Zero, but you know, the classic can.
You get what I mean.
Damn it.
Alright.
Well, I have plans today.
Because some big shit happened last time.
Look, I look like a fucking clown.
Look at this.
I don't know how much I like looking like a clown.
But it's okay.
The robust can.
Here we go.
Oh man.
Actually, hold on, I need to change my keyboard.
Whoops, almost forgot about that.
I have my normal keyboard, and then I of course have my Starcraft keyboard.
I can't use my Starcraft keyboard when I play non-Starcraft games.
It goes without saying, of course.
There we go.
It is now activated.
Oh yeah.
Let me move this over here.
Let's get all ready for Terraria.
Okay, man.
Bunch of shit happened last time.
I killed the Wall of Flesh.
I did all kinds of other things.
I find... found Ori Calcum.
I found Cobalt.
And I have chicken nuggets.
So I'm pretty much on top of the world right now.
Um, look at that.
My inventory is almost sorted.
Upon logging in, isn't that kind of incredible?
That almost never happens.
Is the game a bit loud?
Hold on.
It's okay.
It's fine.
Actually...
Test, test, test.
Yeah, this is fine, I think.
I'm just looking at the meters.
Um, well, yeah.
And then I figured out the teleporters last time.
That's a big one.
Uh, yeah.
Teleporters.
Let's see here.
Oh yeah.
And I got the drill, but I kind of want to replace it anyway, because I... I found out I don't like the sound very much.
Not that it matters too much, I guess.
But...
And here's the thing.
I have Ori Calcum now.
I can make a better one after that anyway, right?
So maybe it's not worth it to replace this with Cobalt just yet.
Hold on.
Uh, my dude?
Asher?
Crafting.
Take this.
Let me just confirm here.
160... Wait, 165?
Yo!
That is an insane upgrade!
What the fuck?
That's not like... This is an insane jump.
What the hell?
I was expecting like 120% maybe.
That's amazing.
Uh, okay.
Well, I'm gonna go find some more Ori Calcum.
That's gotta be the number one thing that I gotta do right now.
And that's actually what I was doing last time.
Yeah, I was going... Power tools!
I just power tooled the platform away.
Let me put that back.
Get power tools.
The platform's away.
Whoops.
God, I look like a clown.
And I really need to get some better looking gear here.
This is just despicable.
It is unheard of.
You can't go fight monsters wearing this shit.
You gotta look the part as well, right?
Okay, hold on.
I need my specialized potion.
Didn't I find a huge deposit of Ori Calcum down here somewhere?
I seem to remember and then I tried to dig it and I failed because like... There it is, oh yeah, it even shows it on the map.
You can mouse over.
Incredible.
I seem to remember it was somewhere to the west.
Get away.
But here we go.
Look at this.
Look at this huge deposit.
Oh, we've got stuff there.
Okay.
I'm also grabbing all this.
Please jump up there.
Thank you.
This fucking drill is so loud.
Yeah, we definitely need to replace that.
Whoo!
Uh, I also had some more...
Where are you?
I have potions of mining.
Don't I?
Maybe it's not on me.
Maybe it's here.
Thorns.
Night owl.
Mining.
Beautiful.
Do that and then also equip the mining thingy.
Let's do this.
Oh my god, it's so... A goblin army!
You know what?
We're heading back.
Let's experiment with some items here.
I found a bunch of weapons.
So the laser rifle is nice.
But I run out of mana so quick that I kind of want something as a backup in case I don't have any mana there.
So what would that be?
Maybe the harp.
Nah.
Hmm.
What is the good weapon I have?
One of the later ones I got.
Didn't I get something really nice?
Oh wait, the Star Fury could be an option?
I just need something to replace.
I have these.
What's in here?
Nothing.
The cell is actually... The cell is Sun Fury.
Oh shit, here we go.
Equipment.
I'm already taking a lot of damage.
Where are they shooting from?
Oh, they're invading.
They're already inside.
Oh, this is actually doing good.
Oh, that's not an enemy.
It kind of looks like a goblin.
Hey, what's up guys?
Oh my god, he's almost dead.
Pip!
Pip, almost dead.
Yeah, something is hitting me.
From somewhere.
Oh my god, Seymour is so low.
The door!
Put it back!
Let's actually... Ah, get away from me.
The sorcerers that spawn are so annoying.
Okay, close the doors.
Let's chill out for a second.
We have goblins up there.
Okay, oh, there we go.
Let's get out of here.
If I just keep swinging, they're not gonna... Oh wait, that's not an enemy.
That's Ludo.
Uh, there's another sorcerer.
Oh my god, Ludo's dead.
Wait, why is that guy... What?!
He didn't take any damage.
What the fuck?
Oh my god, everyone's dying!
Oh my god, it's a disaster.
What the hell is that shadow flame apparition?
Oh, look at this guy.
Oh, I'm dead here.
HP, are you kidding me?
What the fuck?
What is it with this game?
Why is it so hard?
Fucking hell.
I can't do anything here.
This is insane.
Look at this guy flying around.
Yeah, nope.
Yeah, I'm gonna die again.
What can I do?
What the fuck can I do?
I have no idea what to do in this game.
This is fucking crazy.
I have no chance.
Look at how much HP he has.
Is that a boss or something?
There's no health bar, like in the bottom, indicating a boss.
Like, it's just a normal ass enemy.
And he flies everywhere and kills me.
What?
Everyone's dead.
This is chaos.
I have no idea what to do.
Why is this suddenly so fucking hard?
I don't understand.
My god.
Don't wait.
He can shoot through walls, but I can't.
That's fucking great.
This guy can't die.
Yeah, I'm leaving.
See ya.
I don't care about anyone.
Everyone can dive.
I don't really care.
The game is seemingly insanely unfair right now.
Like, there's nothing I can do.
I'm going somewhere else.
Oh, he's following me.
Are you shitting me?
What the actual fuck?
Don't follow me.
Are you serious?
What is this?
What the fuck is this?
What's happening?
I'm running out of mana here.
He does so much.
I have no idea what's happening.
Why is the game so difficult suddenly?
Look at this.
Sparkle was slain.
Hayley was slain.
Fucking everybody is dead.
Why is he so spongy?
Oh my god.
45%.
He spawns these apparitions as well.
I can't leave.
I need to regen mana here.
This is actually a decent strategy here.
Come on.
I'm so oom all the time.
Can I destroy these projectiles?
I can.
That's something.
Okay, I have mana now.
Zoom out a bit.
Come on.
Why does he have so much HP?
What the fuck?
You better drop a weapon that does a million damage per second.
Okay.
You dropped something.
Wait a minute.
Let me take care of this before I die.
Oh, then we have these guys.
Whoa.
Oh my god.
There we go.
What did I get?
Huh?
Oh.
A bow.
Shadowflame bow.
Shoot shadowflame arrows.
No, it doesn't.
I guess I need to find those arrows.
It only shoots those shadowflame arrows, it seems.
No idea how to get them.
Oh my god.
It's not done.
Why is it?
I thought I was done.
Hopefully this will be easier now that the warlock is gone.
Oh, never mind.
There's another one.
Great.
I'm gonna try and see if I can tank his shots with my mace here.
No, it's not really.
Ah, these goddamn projectiles.
Yeah.
Why does he have so much HP?
Just kill me.
I gotta be honest, this is not very fun.
This is kind of stupid.
Like, why has the difficulty jumped a million percent suddenly?
What the fuck is happening?
Everyone is dead.
I have no chance.
What the fuck is happening in this game?
It's a clusterfuck.
So I have to, I have to just run around on my little mine cart, wait for my mana to regen and just... I have to do that forever, I guess, until he dies again.
It's not even a boss, it's just a fucking NPC.
Come on.
Here we go.
God, this weapon sucks.
I need my magic missile.
Do they even have it on me?
I actually do.
I thought it was in my chest, perfect.
As long as I'm up here, the guys on the floor can reach me, that's something.
Out of mana.
And look at this, while I'm dealing with this guy, the bar is not even going up.
Like, I'm not making any progress on this event.
Fuck yeah.
There we go.
What did I get?
Shadowflame knife.
Flick shadowflame on hit.
Now we gotta go back and hope that we can deal with the rest before another one of these spawn.
Did I?
Wait a minute.
Did I drop my money?
Yeah, we're not done yet, there's more.
Does this cost man at all?
Okay, this is a pretty good weapon.
I like this weapon.
It's like throwing knives.
But it doesn't penetrate, so that's... oh my god, he's back again.
This is just dying over and over again, until this is over, I guess.
Or maybe I should just focus on killing the small minions and avoiding that guy, just so I can finish this event.
Oh, yes, so much HP.
It does good damage if you were hitting one target only, and if they don't move around too much.
Like this right here is decent damage right here.
Oh, so many projectiles everywhere, man.
I can't avoid it.
I can't.
I gotta go up here again.
Oh, the knives are falling off after a certain distance.
Gotcha.
100% cleared.
This was painful.
I got another bow.
Cool.
Wait, are we done or not?
Okay, we're done.
Jesus Christ, man.
Are you kidding?
Shoot shadow flame arrows.
The shadow flame knife is... Wait, what the fuck?
What are you doing here?
Look at this house.
Nobody alive.
Everyone is dead.
And there is nothing I could do about that.
Nothing.
Everyone just... The game was like, everyone needs to die now.
What is happening?
Wait, where's uh...
Where's Rosalva?
Did she also somehow die?
And the guy living with her down here is also gone.
Everyone is dead.
All right, well, I can't worry about that now.
First, I have to sort my inventory for two years.
So let's do that.
What's this now?
Oh my god, we're not done.
The doors are being destroyed, it seems.
These fuckers are destroying the door.
The torch method is not working anymore for some reason.
Wait, why can't I... Ah, okay, that's why.
There was a gravestone in front.
Get rid of these fucking graves.
Leave this here.
Actually, leave this on the other side.
Because I already have one on the left.
Let's put one here as well.
Oh my god.
The drill is very effective at removing these.
It's like instant removal.
There.
Let's put all this shit up here.
Red Hat.
Did that drop from Pip when he died?
Probably right.
Who's who's knocking?
Now they can't get in.
What the... why can they not get in now?
Damn.
So tanky.
In viewing station?
That's right, that's also a thing.
A thing I don't understand yet.
Spiky ball.
I mean, that's shit.
I feel like I may have missed something in this game.
Like, this is difficulty...
I don't know.
I just don't have the damage to deal with any of this.
It's wild.
I don't think I'm supposed to die a million times there.
That feels wrong to me.
I don't know what I did.
Okay, let's see here.
Let's just calm down and try and take stock of the situation.
What the fuck do I have that can be used as a good weapon here?
Do I have anything good?
I have Hellfire arrows.
Didn't I get a shotgun at some point?
Where did I put that?
Maybe in here.
Also, I have a mechanical skull.
I don't want to do that.
That seems like suicide.
It's not in here.
Let's sort that.
Oh, wait.
Do this.
Didn't I buy a gun last time?
I'm pretty sure I did.
Or I found one.
I either bought or found one.
Unholy arrow.
Oh, yeah, I bought this actually.
The Cattleigator.
That's right.
Maybe I'll try that again.
And then I also...
Here it is.
Shotgun.
Is anyone gonna move in here again or what?
Everyone is gone.
Hey, Lion Pine survived.
That's something.
So did these guys over here near the ocean.
And Ella somehow also survived.
These guys are so annoying.
Let's look at these bullets situation here.
What are the best bullets I can make?
Also, I actually got to go east.
Look how much HP they have.
Oh, my fucking God.
Damn.
Okay, go here now.
Wait, what?
There are not enough villagers near that pylon to access it.
What the fuck?
Well, that sucks, because everyone's dead.
Real nice.
Also, I need to equip this instead, because it's not actually doing anything.
Right.
Everyone is dead here as well.
Of course.
I was about to talk to Dante, but of course, he's also dead.
I feel like I'm stuck.
Am I just supposed to sit there and wait until they come back or what?
I don't know what to do, man.
Do I even have any bullets anywhere?
Bullets.
Let's check all the chests.
There's none in here.
What about up here?
No.
All right.
Guess I'm not using a gun.
I could use a bow.
No, I can't, because these only shoot shadow flame arrows.
And I don't know how the fuck I make those.
Can't even use that.
I guess I'm stuck with the knife.
That's okay.
Life is actually decent.
The only thing is, it doesn't penetrate.
So in that respect, it kind of sucks against masses of enemies.
I guess I just wait.
I wait for these guys to come back.
What does this one do again?
Magic powers are increased, right?
That's true.
But also, the wizard is dead.
Everyone's dead.
Well, I'm going to go, while I wait for everybody, I'm going to go mine some more Orichalcum.
Actually, hold on.
I already did get some.
Let me quickly check here.
I could make some bars out of this for sure.
Okay, seven.
Is that going to be enough for what I intend to do?
Let's see.
Oh, wait, I needed a special anvil, didn't I?
I can't just straight up do this.
Also, I can actually make one of these weapons.
A repeater?
Isn't that a bow?
Looks like a crossbow in the icon there.
What about the sword?
Is that going to be good?
Let's try it.
I mean, it's got to be good, right?
It's cobalt.
It's the new big thing.
It has a decent range.
Look at that.
It's a big sword.
Big sword, indeed.
Okay.
And what should I have as my...
Oh, yes, I still have the Sabinator, actually.
Ah, but it's so painfully slow.
Where's the other laser weapon of mine?
There.
I think this is still the best I have to use my mana with when I have mana.
Either that or the magic missile.
Well, I'm going to go dig.
We need a bunch of Orichalcum.
We need so much of that.
That's the only real path forward that I see right now is get a shit ton of that and hopefully I can make something that will not feel like shit in combat.
That's the plan.
I'm ready with my drill.
I don't have any potions for detecting, do I?
Let me quickly check.
Thorns, night owl, not in here.
What was this one?
Well, that's the one I just looked at.
This one, man.
Bottled honey.
I think I used all my... Oh, there it is.
Spelunker.
Perfect.
Let's utilize this really well while it lasts.
Just keep going down over here.
Actually, oh wait, there's something there.
No, that's just the... No, that's fossil, isn't it?
That's fossil.
Get out of there.
Walter has arrived.
People are coming back.
But how long will they last?
Oh, is that it?
Yeah!
Now we're talking.
Need all of that?
Thank you.
I need to make one of those special angles and then I have to craft.
Platinum.
Wasn't there also titanium somewhere?
All right, this is a trap.
Get rid of that.
Tungsten bullets.
Let's equip the digging thing again.
And deposit all.
Get everything in there.
Also this one.
Lots of cobalt.
Okay.
What am I, L5C?
Not much.
Oops.
I'm gonna go right here.
And then down this way.
What is that?
A statue of an owl person or something.
There we go.
Found some more.
Let's try this sword.
Not bad.
I like the range on that actually.
Range is good.
I need Dante to come back.
He's not back.
I need to buy bullets.
Let's keep digging.
What is that?
Ah, there we go.
Found some more.
And then we have some gold.
Like this.
Okay.
We're getting a lot of this actually.
This is a good haul so far.
I really hope I get to make something incredible with this.
I need the best of the best of the best, sir.
Okay.
Let's go this way now.
We have a mushroom cave here.
Oh my god.
Look at the HP on that.
Ah, I'm dying to this guy.
Let's put on this.
I don't like the sword very much.
Man, the magic missile comes in clutch every time.
It's the best fucking weapon of the game so far.
Precise Philosopher's Stone.
There's the cooldown of healing potions by 25% dude.
That's big.
That's a big one.
Holy crap.
Hold on.
Put it there.
That's a pretty big one.
25%?
How is that not insane?
Uh oh, there's lava above me.
Why is that chest so tanky?
What is happening?
Oh my god.
Guys, I think I realized something.
I'm just too shit at this game.
I'm not good enough.
I just don't have the skills to play this game.
I need to uninstall.
Where did I die?
There.
I just can't do it.
It's too hard for me.
I've met my match.
It's this game.
Did we go this way?
Yeah, we did.
What is that thing there?
I've been eyeing it every time.
Oh, it's crimting.
Ah, we lost the effect of seeing ore.
That's a bummer.
That's actually such an important flask.
It's like really hard to... Ryan has arrived.
The guide is here again.
Give me that eyeball statue.
Give
me that.
Go down this way.
This is where I went, right?
Yeah.
I do want to check this real quick, though.
Okay.
I need to get used to trying to find ore without having the potion on me.
It's not that easy.
Like, okay, I have to remember this.
This is lead.
Okay.
That is lead.
Ah, wait, go down here.
Ah, all this cobweb is messing with me.
Rock golem!
What's up, dude?
Oh, wow, wow.
My god, it's so tangy.
And now I'm out of mana.
I gotta wait.
Just delete this.
Delete that.
Dual hook?
What?
What is it?
Is there a bigger range?
Maybe it is a bigger range.
Kind of hard to tell.
Is someone dying?
I think someone was stepping in lava just now.
I probably died down here.
75 gold.
Thank god I got that back.
Got cobbled here.
Very good.
And we have a guy coming in.
There we go.
Oops.
I need to find an item that will make my magic missile not cost any mana.
That's the key here.
Delete that.
Orange blood rod.
So what's with the dual hook?
How far of a range are we talking here?
Is that?
Please.
It goes to there.
Let me try and equip the other one.
I think it's a little longer.
Okay.
But what's the point of that?
Is it to just keep the momentum going or what?
It's like there's less of a cooldown in between.
Okay, that's pretty neat.
Pretty neat.
Okay, I don't need to be on the lookout for this ore now because I have trouble seeing it without the spelunken potion.
In fact, maybe I should just go back and make another spelunken potion.
Now that the guide is there, people tell me what I need to make it.
Mackenzie, the zoologist, has arrived.
Was that the previous hailing?
I forgot.
What's happening here?
Need ore?
Oh!
Yeah.
You know what?
This one is actually amazing for detecting traps.
This item here.
Maybe I don't want to go down there, huh?
Seems like a bad idea.
A skeleton archer.
What's that?
Tin.
Oh, whoa!
Ah, that's not the trappy thingy.
Yeah, I'm gonna go back.
I need to make that potion.
I can't spot this ore otherwise.
Okay, Ryan.
Ryan, Ryan, Ryan.
Actually, I have a lot of orichalcum.
Let's make that into bars.
And then using these bars, I shall make oreichalcum anvil.
12.
Okay.
Let's throw that down somewhere.
Ah!
Get rid of that.
I need it down here, though.
It's kind of important.
Okay.
Now, what can I make?
We need weapons.
No, actually, we need the pickaxe, so we can find more of this.
Halberd.
The damage looks shit on these.
Bone javelin.
I mean, I gotta make a pickaxe.
There's just no question.
The pickaxe has to be prioritized here.
Firstly, because it's not gonna make the brr sound.
And secondly, it's better.
By a lot.
It's even a superior one.
Can mine adamantite and titanium.
Fuck yeah.
Let's try and find that.
I need to make a titanium fucking blaster.
And start blasting everyone.
So anyway, I started that.
Now I want to test.
Oh, Danger Sense!
Oh, not Danger Sense, Spelunker.
Let's make that immediately.
I don't think I have any water on me.
Water, water, water, water, water, water.
Where did I put that?
I think I may have used it all.
I did use a lot last time.
Do I not have any glass?
So we need sand to make glass.
Let's see, do we have sand?
We do have some sandstone.
Will this do?
Pardon sandblock, that will probably do, right?
Glass?
Yep.
And I can't make more glass here, right?
No.
Bottles?
52.
And then all of these bottles we need to fill up.
Some water, which we have down here.
Okay, make bottled water now.
Okay, I need an extended period now with no attacks, so I can focus on re-stabilizing in this game.
I just need to re-fucking-stabilize, because things have gotten out of hand.
And we need those things to be in the hand, not out of the hand.
Out of the hand is bad.
Get rid of the door, because it sucks.
Get rid of this wood, because it also makes me angry.
Wood makes me angry!
Okay.
Oh, it has a 12% size increase.
That's like a modifier.
That's interesting.
Okay, let me also make these.
Because why wouldn't I?
Now, tell me once again how to make the Spelunker Potion.
Now we have to go through all of them to see which one is which.
There it is.
It needs Blink Root, Moon Glow, and Gold.
Blink Root, Moon Glow, and Gold.
Blink Root, Moon Glow, and...
Gold.
Nice.
Let's see how many we can get.
Six.
Very good.
The cooking pot, let's put that there.
Okay.
Do this.
Now, the damaged Cobalt Drill.
Let's start selling some stuff.
Ella.
I need you to buy this.
Honestly, buy this as well.
I'm not a big fan of that.
In fact, any melee weapon?
Melee?
I'm not a big fan of it.
It's awkward the way he attacks in the direction your character faces.
So sometimes when you mouse to the left, he still attacks to the right because your character is facing right.
And that is super awkward for me.
Maybe it's a me thing, but that's just not very intuitive.
So that always fucks me up.
That's why I want to go range it.
Okay.
Sandstone stuff.
We put that back in here.
Or goes in here.
Dirt.
Also goes in here.
Link root can go back where it came from.
And now we go digging again.
This time with a superior Pig-axe.
Let's wait with the potion.
Not yet.
Wait until we get a little further down.
In fact, let's try to go somewhere else.
Let's try to go to somewhere completely different.
Maybe there's a bigger chunk of Orichalcum.
Or maybe even Titanium.
That's the thing I want to try and find.
Now that I have the ability to mine it.
Nobody has arrived here yet, so rip.
Wow, that was a dramatic death.
Do you hear that now?
There is some big creature lurking somewhere, I think, when that sound comes.
Oh wait, I don't have any mana.
I need my knife.
Did I sell the... I didn't sell the knife, did I?
Whatever.
Let's just keep going.
I'm gonna go down here now and check for Orichalcum.
These guys are dangerous.
Oh no.
Let's get rid of them first.
What the fuck is that?
A pixie!
Oh wait a minute, wasn't there something about a pixie leading me to something?
Maybe not, kill it.
Pixie Dust.
For some reason I got the Dark Souls vibe there, that it would disappear if I didn't kill it quick, you know?
And I would get some loot out of it.
I have to consult with the guide again.
Another one.
Thanks.
If Pixie Dust, I'm gonna try and give that to Ryan, of course.
Woah!
A unicorn!
What?!
Kill it!
Foul beast!
Unicorn horn.
What the fuck?
Oh, something's shooting lasers now.
What the hell is that now?
A gastropod.
What the hell?
Murder it all.
Oh, that was a dramatic one.
Nice.
Okay, I'm gonna go dig here.
Actually, this looks kind of weird, doesn't it?
Have I been here before?
What the fuck is this?
What is this?
Pearls?
Wait.
What?
Have I been here before?
I don't know.
Maybe I have.
Blessed with Cobalt.
I don't know, man.
Hey!
That's why I have so much mana.
I keep picking up these mana stars.
Come here.
I'm actually intrigued by this area.
There we go, thank you.
And what the fuck is this?
Hold on.
Eh?
You hear that?
Oh, there!
I'm gonna go kill it.
Oh, actually, I'm gonna try and catch it with my botnet.
Oh, what the?
Shooting lasers and shit.
Uh, mining?
Ah.
This one is not that quick, man.
I expected this Pig-axe to be superior.
The hell?
Kind of disappointing, Pig-axe.
Uh-oh.
Okay, let me try and see if I can catch it.
Oh, it doesn't work.
It was worth a try.
I'm losing some HP here.
I need to find a way to make those health potions that give more health.
It's gotta be a priority for me.
Oh, God, here we go.
Okay.
Thank you.
Oh!
Listen to this music, it's different.
Yo, this is a different biome!
But is it, though?
I've been here before, look!
There's torches everywhere, what the fuck?
I could've... like, I've been here.
Pearlstone block.
Did something fall from the sky?
Is this, like, another type of meteor-type deal?
Where this area got converted?
Orykalkum, nice.
So weird.
Oh, I have so many things to show the guide.
Oh, come on.
It's confused.
Ah, it's not dead yet!
Oh, my God!
Fuck!
I hate being oom.
Now...
I have my money here.
Is it gonna be picked up by someone?
That's the question.
Actually, you know what?
While I'm here.
Ryan.
Tell me about all these new items I found.
Pixie Dust.
Yes!
Oh, but I need Crystal Shard.
Oh, that's the thing I need.
Cast a controllable rainbow?
Well, you know what?
Imagination is not something the developers of this game are lacking.
Let me say that.
Showers meteors.
Really?
But Soul of Light.
I don't know how to get that.
I mean...
By killing that wall of flesh, I got one, I think.
But...
I need to kill ten of those?
Oh, what?
That seems crazy.
Some is a magical fairy.
I do have a bell.
But I don't have all these souls.
Unfortunately.
Okay.
What about the Pearl Stone?
Hallowed?
Wait a minute!
The Hello.
My fucking god, is that the...
Is this the Hello?
Has it been the Hello this entire time?
Have I missed this?
From the beginning?
Why is Hano over here?
Whoops!
Whoops, I didn't mean to do that, but that's okay.
Okay.
So, alright.
That's the mystery solved.
That's something.
Now, Unicorn Horn.
I can make a rainbow rod with that.
And I can also make...
Super Mana Potion requires Crystal Shards.
Crystal Shards!
My guess is they can be found in the Hello then.
That seems like the place.
You know?
Of all the places...
That's gotta be the one.
Also, eat a chicken nugget.
And also...
Let's eat some of this, because we are not strong enough.
We just aren't.
Thorns.
Ah, let's save the swiftness, get a...
Yeah, Regen is good.
Cattle in the nurse.
She's back.
Where's the gunman?
Did he move in over here somewhere?
Oh yeah!
Fucking dead!
Oh wait, I can't do this yet.
Okay.
I'm gonna see if I can buy some bullets.
And then I'm gonna try the shotgun once more.
Because that seemed promising.
I just didn't have bullets last time.
Andre!
Yeah, that's what I got it.
I got it from him.
When it was a chance to save ammo.
See, that would be nice if you're about to fight a boss.
You put this down, right?
So...
Tungsten?
Uh...
Hold on.
There's definitely better bullets I can make, right?
Let me see here.
Oh, this one?
Wait, endless musket pouch?
Oh, but it's only gonna make...
It's only gonna shoot muskets.
Okay.
Well, let's see here.
Crystal cursed the bullet.
Ah, here we go.
Chases after your enemy.
Oh, that sounds pretty dope.
Chlorified bar.
Wow.
Cursed bullet?
I don't know how to get any of this.
Crystal bullet.
Ah, crystal shard.
I guess I'm going with tungsten for now.
Didn't I have a million?
Did I sell all my bullets?
I think I did.
Uh...
Need a hand there?
There's something unusually warm about you.
I'm not sure how to place it, but keep walking in that direction.
Thank you.
I mean...
There's also something warm about you.
Give me a shit ton of these, I guess.
Like that.
And then we make them into tungsten.
Because that's the best I can make right now.
Wait, I think I have what I need.
I just need to be in the right spot here.
Tungsten bullet.
Oh!
For some reason I thought one musket ball would make 70 tungsten.
Of course not.
I need way more of these.
Oh wait, he actually...
Hold on, he sells them directly, but that's probably not worth it.
I can make them myself.
Let's do like 900 or something.
Maybe that's not even enough.
You use bullets quick, right?
Something like that.
Let's do that.
And then we make...
More.
Need these.
There we go.
Okay.
Let's see now.
Shotgun.
Oh, that was in my chest, wasn't it?
Or in one of these.
Shotgun.
And I also had the other one.
Let me actually try both again.
I had the...
Hold on.
Is it in here?
Where's the Gatling gun?
Oh, that's 80 gold coins in here.
Let's actually put the money in there.
Ice is the party girl.
Where is that weapon?
Actually, keep this here for now.
The Gatlegator, that's it.
Highly inaccurate, but that's okay.
If I go close with this, that's all that matters, right?
This one is also, I guess, highly inaccurate.
But again, if you're close...
It's still kind of accurate.
But it fires in the spread, yeah.
Okay.
23.
And how much did the laser do?
My laser gun?
39.
But I have to remember, I'm also wearing the...
the magic set right now.
So if I can do a set with Ranget, that's going to help a lot.
So, let me actually do that.
And the best part is, I think, if I just make the right helmet, I think the rest of the set will adjust, right?
Let's see.
Yes, look at that.
Look at that.
28 now.
And remember, 28 per bullet.
And it shoots like four bullets.
That's like 100 if you hit.
That's a decent chunk of damage.
But will it penetrate?
I don't think it will.
So that's like the thing, right?
That is the thing with that.
Now this one, kind of neat.
Okay.
It seems good.
Good start.
Now let's revisit these items, because some of them give me magic damage, which I don't need right now.
This one can go away for now.
This one is kind of sick.
We definitely keep that one.
This one as well.
The brain of confusion.
Is that really still good?
I think it is, right?
Increases critical chance after dodge.
Oh, after being struck.
No, after dodge.
Wait, after dodge?
Oh yeah, when you dodge an attack randomly.
Okay, gotcha.
I think the next step is to find the right thingy there.
Hold on.
This one is not bad.
But can I do better?
I think it's fine for now.
Wait, heal the user on hit.
Maybe this is nice to use when I'm low on HP, maybe.
A forceful bat-bat.
Maybe I could bat some bats with this.
All right, well, we got to try it.
Let's go back down.
With our potions.
Deposit stuff.
Put this in here.
And this looks good for now.
Let's go.
I'm going to go back to the Hello area.
I'm not done there.
I need to make a mage tower in that biome.
Oh wait, not this weapon.
Let's try this.
And not bad.
I like it.
I do like it.
A little slow though, but against single enemies like that, maybe not the best when they're so small, it's probably the best for a boss weapon, right?
Oops.
Nice.
What is up here?
A magical tree.
Wait, where's my axe?
Oh, did I get rid of the axe?
Whoops.
All right, it's actually kind of hard to aim with.
Bro, you have a shit ton of HP.
Yeah, hold on, let me try changing this back.
Let me try this.
It's very inaccurate, yeah.
Oh,
another unicorn.
Good thing is I'm not losing mana doing this.
I got to say though, this weapon kind of sucks.
Jesus Christ, I need something way more substantial.
These enemies are so tangy.
Fuck!
Wait, what's that?
A cookie.
Nice.
That's my money.
Wait, what is that?
Oh, okay.
Like, all this whole area is changed.
There's new music.
Very weird.
I wonder where I can find titanium.
Let me put on the thingy.
Spillunker.
You know what?
I bet your titanium is all the way in the bottom.
That would make total sense.
It's probably all the way down here.
Oh, I should not do this here.
Hold on.
We're going back.
Is it raining blood?
Oh no.
I don't know how I feel about the shotgun.
A werewolf!
Oh my god, this is...
Oh!
Okay!
1600 health, what the hell?
How much does this do?
Look at this bullet sponginess!
Like, what is happening?
Why is it like this?
What happened, man?
I'm not doing any... I'm tickling them!
Meanwhile, they're two-shotting me.
Oh my...
Oh, here we go again.
Everyone's gonna die.
I don't even know what's going on.
What is going on in this game, dude?
Why is every weapon so shit?
All right, guess everyone dies again.
I don't really care.
You can die for a like here.
Bye-bye.
I'm gonna go straight into the underworld.
See if I can make a run to get some...
Get some superior...
Oh, wow.
Nevermind.
I need to change it again.
Wait, what's this?
Dark shard?
What is that?
Hey, yo.
What's this?
Oh, shit.
Oh, please leave me alone!
What the hell is that?
Angry Nimbus?
Isn't that a type of cloud?
Does look like a cloud, actually.
Okay, who else wants some?
Come here.
Who wants to taste the shotgun?
You?
Nimbus?
Is it raining on me?
Is that what it's trying to do?
Yeah, look, it's raining on me.
Damn.
Oh, another cloud.
Oh, my God.
This weapon sucks.
Dick!
We need another one.
We gotta go back to the magic...
The magic missile, dude.
The magic missile.
Where are you?
We need it.
We need that fucking magic missile.
Uh, also put this one back on.
Uh, there, I guess.
Let's summon one of these.
Let's summon another one.
And then, where did I put my hat?
There.
Okay, we're back to this now.
Good.
Magic missile.
Equipped.
And in the number one slot, let's put a...
Sure, let's try this.
Let's have fun with that.
We have everything we need.
Let me have to try this.
Oh, my God.
Look at this, it's way better.
Oh, magic missile, how have I missed you?
Or even this one is also pretty good.
Look, it's way better!
My God.
I mean, it's not great, but it's better.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Stop, stop!
Wait, is this one bouncing off of him?
Oh, Ryan is dead again.
Oh, I'm out of mana.
See, that's the issue with this mana.
Oh, my God.
Now, he's dead as well.
Everyone dies.
I can't even kill an enemy with one mana bar.
That's how tanky and spongy they are.
There's too many.
Guys, I don't know what to do, dude.
I don't know what to do in this.
I feel like...
I don't get it.
Whenever there's any type of combat, I may as well just tab out.
There's no reason to even try and fight these guys.
It's insane.
I can't even ask the guide about this fucking thing anymore, because he's dead.
My God, man.
Where's the randomly gold on the floor there?
What's this?
Why is that star purple?
Huh.
No mana.
Honestly, I'm tempted to restart this entire game and not choose expert, because this is not very fun.
This is completely fucked up.
What's that?
The clown.
The game is clowning on me.
Like, legitimately.
That's what it feels like.
At this point, I'm just...
You know, getting clowned on.
Come on.
I can't even organize.
I don't even...
I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
Let me think.
I've had enough of your shit.
Get off my lawn.
That's right!
Be scared!
Be scared of the lawnmower!
Get off my lawn!
You motherfucker!
Fuck off!
That's right.
Get off my damn lawn!
See, now they're running!
Ha!
Adhesive bandage.
Immunity to bleeding.
That's cool, I guess.
Wish I could ask the guide about it, but he's dead.
Alright, lawnmower is now confirmed the way to deal with these guys.
God, I hate my inventory!
Quickstack.
Guys, I'm overwhelmed.
I'm overwhelmed.
I feel like I may have done something I shouldn't have in this game.
And it all happened after I killed the wall of flesh.
I feel like I should not have done that.
I can't kill anything.
It's fucking insane.
But...
There is one hope.
And that is to keep going down.
And try and find some ore.
So we can try and make a weapon that doesn't suck balls.
That's my only hope.
Anakin.
You're my only hope.
Or whatever that...
I forgot that quote.
We gotta go dig.
We gotta go find some stuff.
Whoops.
What's this?
Titainum.
Heck yeah!
Yes, please!
More of that!
That's platinum.
There's actually some... is that?
No, that's just cobbled up here.
What about up here?
I don't even want to mine the cobalt.
I want better ones.
Zoom out.
Get me to the...
Keep going down here, I guess.
Oh, it's useless and water.
That makes sense.
We have a little trap here.
Active stone block.
Wait, what's going on there?
Would you look at that over there?
Oh, wait, this is...
Yep.
Wait, this is Orykalkum.
Jester's arrow.
Oh my god.
Thorns.
Oh, my inventory.
Fucking deposit everything.
I thought Minecraft inventory management was tough.
It's nothing.
Minecraft is a walk in the park.
The inventory.
Go down this way.
Actually, equip the thingy.
Oh, actually, this is the... I need that one equipped.
It's quite important.
Let's replace this one.
There we go.
Look how fast I'm going through tin.
Is that it?
Titainum?
Yeah!
Now we're talking.
Very excited to find out what I can make with that.
It better be a weapon that slaps.
Or I will riot.
More!
Hell yeah.
Keep going down.
Getting dangerous.
In fact, let me just do that.
Now it's not dangerous.
Yep, there's more here.
Someone's dying in the lava.
Music to my ears, honestly.
What if I make a moat around my fucking house with lava?
Be careful here.
I wonder if I can do that.
Maurice has arrived.
Let me grab...
Let me see here.
Yeah, just go further down.
Honestly, I'm at the point where I don't even want cobalt.
I want the good stuff.
Oh, did the potion wear off?
Oh, I can't find it.
I think I used them all.
Oh, hold on.
That's Ori Kalkum.
Very nice.
That's actually a lot of it.
Why does this look scary?
I thought something was about to collapse.
This one is actually not bad.
I do like the flame thingy.
Very similar to Magic Missile, though.
Which is good, because Magic Missile is, so far, best in slot.
Okay.
Do we see anything?
What the hell is that right there?
I can't tell.
Is the guide back?
Shit, he's not.
Unless he went somewhere else.
Wait, we're Selva's over here now.
Oh!
It's a spider.
Look at how much HP it has.
I'm out of mana now.
Ah!
Come on!
Jesus Christ.
There we go.
Look how much cobwebs we got here.
What the heck?
Wait, why is the shooting so fast now?
Ah, fuck.
Am I crazy, or is this suddenly shooting insanely fast?
It didn't shoot that fast before.
God, am I tired of walking up here to these chests and performing the ritual.
Okay, new plan.
New plan.
I've had enough of this now.
Completely new plan.
Gimme stone blocks.
I need my axe.
Axe, axe, axe, axe, axe.
Where did I put my axe?
It's not here.
Is it here?
Where is my axe?
I'm gonna go here now.
Get rid of all this.
Do I have dirt?
Jeff has arrived, finally.
Jeff, where are you?
Oh my God, why are you over there?
God damn it.
Jeff!
You get to be here now.
All right, Jeff, come here.
I'm gonna let you reload so you can come here.
And he's not.
This system is so random.
Sometimes they instantly reload here, sometimes they don't, I don't understand.
Why it doesn't work.
Ah, I wanna ask him about the titanium.
But here's the thing, we can probably just make titanium bars.
Or not.
Wait, is this one?
Why can I not make titanium bars?
I don't know.
Probably need some random ass crafting station.
That I gotta ask the guide about.
Anyway, I'm gonna continue my little plan over here.
Get rid of that.
And this.
Wait, it's very fast on dirt, that's nice.
That's very nice.
And then,
let's see how long, how far up do we want this.
Something like that.
Now I need to make some stuff.
Click this.
Wow, that did almost nothing.
Put that there.
This there.
Put it back there.
Delete it!
Something like that.
Give me that.
So let's see here.
Did I have any more wood at all?
I mean, I have this wood.
Works with me.
Actually, wait a minute.
Turn this into wood.
And see where it goes when I click here.
Okay, I don't have any then.
That's okay.
That is okay.
I actually make them now.
Wait, trapped chest.
What now?
Can I just make a normal ass chest?
Why
can I not make a chest?
What?
Jeff, you have made it.
Tell me how to make a fucking chest.
Workbench?
Ugh, iron.
But you don't need iron to make a trapped chest?
What?
Iron, iron, iron.
Lead accounts.
I'm pretty sure, at least.
Chest, chest.
Workbench is here.
There.
Alright, this is my attempt to solve shortcomings of the game.
And
then...
We're gonna make many layers of chests here.
There we go.
Because I've had it once and for all with this fucking inventory system.
It's driving me mad.
I'm actually losing my mind.
We need more.
Get rid of all the wood.
Thank you.
All of it.
Got a million HP.
Okay.
Let's make some shelves.
That seems good.
We need more chests.
In fact, I have a better idea here.
This is gonna be a duo thing.
Oh god, which one is it?
Which one is the fucking work?
Is that the workbench here?
Did I run out of lead?
Oh, that's why.
Hold on.
I can remove these.
I can't remove them when they're full.
So I have to manually...
That's what I feared.
That ain't happening.
Uh, really?
Hoot.
Amazing.
Okay, new plan.
I'm gonna do this.
I'm gonna split this in half here.
This side I will fill up with planters.
This side will be purely chests.
Because I think it may be too many chests.
But then again, maybe I'll regret that later.
You know?
Maybe it's not gonna be too many chests.
Maybe I'm lowballing it even now.
Who knows?
But that's the plan.
Also, get rid of that outfit.
I'm gonna take from here to there.
Split it halfway.
And we're gonna plant shit over here.
And I'm gonna steal some chests from this area over here.
This is gonna be the storage area only.
It's gonna be the crafting fucking area.
You know?
Everything related to crafting needs to go there.
And it needs to be organized.
Otherwise...
I just can't.
We gotta find a solution for this.
It is just so important.
Now what else works?
Iron bar?
Use that.
This is the crafting bench.
I can make mahogany.
Why not?
Make a bit of that.
And...
Then, I'm actually gonna take all these chests from there now.
Let's put some lights in here.
Just like that for now.
And...
Then I wanna do this.
Now these two can stay.
In.
Everything in for now.
These two are definitely need to stay here.
In.
Stays.
Now we gotta do this!
Loot all.
And get ready for some riveting gameplay.
Okay...
How do I wanna do this?
We could have one row or column of one thing.
And then...
Maybe make a separator between them.
Or something.
Let's see here.
It's like maybe I wanna make a little space in between.
Like that.
And...
Maybe the bottom row...
Should actually not contain any chests.
Maybe that's where I put all the crafting stuff.
You know?
Crafting stuff on the bottom row.
Only chests up here.
That seems reasonable to me.
Now we put everything in here.
There.
Is that gonna be enough?
Let's say that's enough.
In height.
And then I wanna seperator here so this is gonna be...
Weapons.
Only weapons!
Nothing else.
This is going to be accessories.
And maybe I'll make that one bigger.
Because there's just so many of them.
But then again, I do have a lot of accessories that are duplicates of each other.
That I can just throw the shit out.
Right, so...
Hopefully...
Yeah, I'm gonna have...
Two for each.
Let's do that.
Now where are the rest of the chests?
Are they still in here?
They are.
Good.
Let me do this.
The good news is, I can always replace the look of a chest without having to empty it.
That is such a nice thing.
Uh, loot all.
And we go over here.
And I also have more mahogany chests on me.
Okay, so all these are gonna be accessories for now.
Let's see.
Okay, none of these are actually... Actually, hold on.
We should also have a vanity chest area.
Stuff like this, you know?
Oh, this is also vanity.
Uh, this is a material thingy.
Oh, none of these are actually.
Okay, I think I still want construction as a category.
Maybe that can be all the way over here or something.
Yeah, something like that.
I need more chests.
I have some empty ones, right?
That's empty.
That's empty now.
Almost empty.
Give me those.
Let's put some weapons in here.
Oh, this chest is full as fuck.
Use this as a buffer for now.
Deposit everything in there.
These are all like...
A lot of them are accessories.
Let's see.
Nope.
Yep.
Then we got this one.
That one.
Ice mirror.
You know what?
Delete this shit.
All these magic mirrors need to sell them.
Or delete them.
Hannah was back and it has the same name as well.
Here you go.
You can have this one as well.
I don't want this shit.
Gold helmet.
There you go.
Take that as well.
Okay, more of these.
Thank you.
Actually, let me start selling immediately.
Have it.
You can have that as well.
I think this is... maybe this is not even enough.
Maybe this entire thing needs to be chests.
Yeah.
We need to make this entire room chests.
Go in there.
Vanity, vanity.
Key?
No.
No, I don't even want to sell it.
I just want to get rid of it.
Money means nothing to me right now.
Absolutely nothing.
That goes in.
This is starting to look like something.
This one I can sell.
I also have so many of these.
You can also be sold.
Two shark baits.
Sell one of them.
Get rid of that one.
Hano?
Where did you go?
Oh, I can talk to you.
Take this, that one, that one, that one.
This one sucks.
You can have it.
And back we go.
Oh, that actually only puts things in there.
That's already in there.
When I use that button, of course.
So all these different wants here are kind of weird.
The Uncombering Stone.
See, on one hand, this is amazing.
But on the other hand, it's also terrible.
Because I don't want to never pick up things again.
That's terrible.
I want to be able to filter.
And say, never pick up dirt again, for example.
But everything else.
You know?
This one is useless.
Get rid of it.
Useless.
I have two of these.
Get rid of one of them.
Don't even want to sell it.
Okay.
I guess...
I'm staring myself blind on this.
So weapons, materials, or accessories.
And then we have...
What should this be?
Vanity, maybe?
And I don't even know what that is.
I don't know what category this could be.
My best guess is Michelinius, but that's a slippery slope, isn't it?
Yeah.
Let's only put things in here that say vanity.
Otherwise, I lose my sanity.
What is vanity?
Can I not filter by vanity?
Or something.
Vanity, vanity...
These two go in here.
Now, weapons...
I should have maybe put armor here, right?
Weapons, armor.
Although three chests for weapons should be more than enough.
And three chests just for armor should also be more than enough.
Right?
Like, realistically, how much am I going to be using?
How many different weapons, right?
Probably not that many different weapons.
So maybe in these chests I put all the armor.
Like this.
B-head gear, you know?
This is vanity.
Let's put...
...enja...
This goes in here.
I don't know where to put stuff like this.
Like, okay, this could be...
...minions or summons.
Or something like that.
Go in there, sort this.
Oh, wait, no, no, no.
Wait, wrong one.
This is vanity.
It goes there.
No, it's... fuck, wrong one.
The slime just killed a rabbit, I think.
I'm sapped of energy.
I can't even think straight trying to sort this.
Here.
But the problem is...
I already have one of these here, right?
So I have to double-check all these chests to make sure I don't have duplicates.
So this one actually gets... just puts stuff that gets sold there.
Do I have a stool already?
I do.
Sell that.
Do I... Warding acolyte?
This is another one of these.
I don't think I have one of those, so they go in here.
Depth meter, already have one that gets sold.
Magic mirror, I should have one of those already.
This is a...
...minion.
Radar.
Sort.
Okay, I have two of these.
One can be sold.
Two of these, sell it.
Sort.
Okay.
I'll take these here and put them in here instead.
No duplicates.
Okay, let's go sell.
Maurice.
You can buy all these things.
Why can't I... Okay, I can control-click it.
That's great.
Okay, so this one, let's put all the stuff that...
Let's put that stuff in here.
Wait a minute.
Accessories.
Here's the weapons.
Okay.
At least that's sort of sorted.
These two go in that chest.
Oh, this one could be sold, right?
These are all like... No, this is all the different wands and stuff.
Weapons.
There we go, there we go.
Honestly, let's just... No, I need to have something equipped in case some shit happens, right?
Gotta be ready for that.
Now.
There, there.
Okay, this is starting to look like something.
It's starting to look like something.
Magic mirror.
A mirror.
Okay, the bat goes in here.
That goes in there.
I'm just gonna sort this from the get-go.
Diamonds.
Snake charmer.
You know what?
I'm gonna sell stuff like that.
I will never use that.
There's no apparent use for it, so you don't get rid of this as well.
And that.
Do we even want this stuff?
I don't know, maybe.
I don't want this either.
Maybe that's what we need here.
We need a good purge of items.
I've been hoarding for too long.
Deposit all for now and then go over here, grab all the weapons.
We're gonna deposit all of that in the chest.
Hold on, let's sell duplicates first.
So we're gonna do a sort.
Shop.
Sell.
We have three of these, man.
Insane.
Sell these, sell that.
This one.
There.
Sell the arrows.
And that one.
This one.
I'm just gonna sell shit that I don't think I'll ever use.
This is not a material, not a material.
It's shit, all of this is shit.
This is the material, so I'll keep that.
Godly dark lands.
Maybe it's good, I don't know.
There's a six mana water bolt.
This one is a special one, because that is related to the whole...
the wave defense thing.
Enchanted sword is a material.
Yeah, all these different swords actually go together and make something great later on.
Nice.
That's a good purge.
That's a good purge right there.
What else do we have?
Oh yeah, all these.
Oh yeah, I have this one as well.
Jagged magnet flower.
And then this one.
Nectar.
Baby hornet.
Let's sell some stuff again.
Man, these ones do a lot of damage.
But they just...
Are they...
Use this nine mana.
The houndier shootiest.
Doesn't seem that good.
Get rid of it.
Get rid of this.
Go on it.
Get rid of these as well.
Wait.
Ancient cobalt.
Six defense.
Eight.
Okay, so it's actually worse.
Oh wait, no, no.
Don't buy it.
Do not buy it.
You know what?
You can have this.
Magic myth.
I have already one of those, don't I?
Let's put this...
What is this?
Hasty in it.
Yeah.
You can have this as well.
What about...
No, I want to keep that.
Tool belt.
What does this do again?
Increases block placement range.
I want to put that on one of my other outfits.
We should have a builder outfit.
You know?
Something we put on when we build things.
And we'll give all kinds of buffs there.
Oh yeah, I have a watch here.
In fact, let's take these for now.
And then we can sort all this shit later.
Yeah.
We're going to get rid of all that first.
And then we decide later on.
So this is vanity stuff.
Can we sort this by vanity maybe?
Wait.
This is not vanity.
It's the actual thing.
Let's get rid of it.
Get rid of that.
This is a material.
We want to keep it.
Okay.
Let's see here.
I already have a radar.
I don't have a weather radio or that.
This goes in here.
This one.
That one.
Okay.
Let's get sold.
Weapons.
Maybe I should sort the weapons by melee, range it, and magic.
How about that?
Let's do that actually.
Instead of just randomly, you know, let's make it from the beginning.
Very nice.
Arrange it, go here.
And then up here we can put stuff like scepters and stuff like that.
And this sort of stuff.
And summons.
All that.
Uh, yep.
Let's see.
Masterful magic missile.
This one gets sold then.
And you go.
It's not a material actually.
Let's sell that.
Sell that.
This is a range it to, like, yeah.
That counts as range it.
I would say.
We have the shotgun, this one, and that one.
This one.
So many depth meters.
I already have a depth meter, don't I?
I do.
These get sold.
This one stays for now.
You're there.
There we go.
Oh, loom, I did accidentally pick that up.
You hear that?
Then we have this mess right here.
Let's wait with that.
Let's take all the things that we have already sort of categorized.
All these are material stuff.
Let's leave this here for now.
Banners.
Anything here?
Okay.
Potions.
Now here I have a bunch of shit.
Let's see.
Okay.
Gems.
Oars.
I guess food or whatever.
Man, I have a shit seat.
I have so many empty bottles here.
Take all.
What's in here?
Oh, yeah, right.
Okay.
Let's go sort these.
Empty bucket.
And you go there.
I guess this one is also goes in here, yeah.
Okay, so we have weapons here.
And armor goes here.
Or maybe this is all weapons slash armor.
Like right side armor, left side weapons.
Oh, we also have this one.
Get all that.
So in here we put stuff like that.
Right?
Didn't put anything else here.
Right, I put armor here.
Let's start with the bottom one.
And here we put that.
There we go.
Actually put this here.
Let's do that for now.
Can always replace them later.
That's the good thing.
You can replace a chest without removing the inside.
Stuff.
Oh, these actually go in the...
chest over here.
Actually, this axe I kind of need.
Or do I?
I should make a cobalt axe, I guess.
Or something like that.
Oh, we can sell this one.
Go in there.
See, this is more like a utility item.
Maybe I always keep that on me.
You know, like the own hammer.
The bucket is useful.
So this, weapons, armor.
This is all accessories.
Vanity items.
And here we can start something new.
We could have...
I don't know.
What could be in there?
Potions, maybe.
Maybe this side is potions.
The other side, something else.
Hold on.
I see items that need to be sorted.
What's in here?
Godly mace is a material.
Snow pants.
No.
Don't want it.
This is vanity.
See?
Vanity.
Yeah, I also need a chest just for material.
Straight up, just stuff like lens.
You know, or like monster drops.
Something like that.
This always stays in my inventory.
Wait, most pure and hallowed grass.
Hallowed grass?
The fuck you mean?
Grass can become hallowed?
There's my potions of return!
The wonders that turn up when you start cleaning, huh?
Just like real life.
Man-eater banner.
I guess with the weapons...
We could also put like ammo.
We should have a chest for ammo and stuff like that.
Right?
So...
My God.
This is so overwhelming.
And the worst part is, it's just for making the inventory easier to manage.
Let's say this one in the middle is material.
Let's just make a decision right now.
Material it is.
What is material now?
Material.
Yeah.
I kind of want a chest just for blocks like this.
Because that is actually a separate thing, even though it's also a material.
You know?
And I also want one just for ores, even though it's all still a material.
So it's a little bit hard to know.
How you should do it.
These are also materials.
Yeah, this one can be blocks.
Let's do that.
Blocks in there.
And let's decide this is construction.
This is construction.
Ninja shirt.
That goes up here.
Or there, actually.
That's not vanity.
Yeah, it's technically not vanity.
That's not vanity either.
Sort.
Why is this...
Oh, never mind.
Ninja.
And...
In there.
Slime hook.
Hero ale.
Would you like to purchase some shit from me?
You know what?
Get rid of these.
Get rid of this one as well.
And that.
Sell all the things.
In fact, I hate the banners.
They're annoying, they're cumbersome, they're just...
It's not worth the effort.
I don't want to spend time putting them up.
It's too much fucking work.
Get rid of it.
I need to seriously...
simplify this game.
Because it's just...
I need to eliminate all that bullshit.
Otherwise, it's all about inventory management.
24-7.
So I need to absolutely decide what not to pick up from now on.
It's the only way.
Material.
Grab all that.
Let's go fill up the chest.
Okay.
I guess this goes in here, that goes in here.
That goes in there.
This also is interesting.
The solar tablet fragment is very intriguing to me.
Get rid of that.
In there.
The bomb fish.
I kind of want to sell that.
These are clearly materials that belong in here, I feel like.
So this is a nicely...
easy decision to make.
Material.
This one.
I guess it is.
But it's like a special material, right?
Fuck it, it goes in.
It goes in.
Material there.
Okay.
And then we need a potion chest.
Maybe the ones on the very right shall be potions and...
Let's say potions on the left and on the right here we can have seeds and stuff to make potions with.
You know?
I think that's good.
Let's just put all the potions in here for now.
Everything.
We may have to make this even longer.
This may not be enough space.
Take all that.
And then...
more potions.
Potions, potions, potions.
Lots of potions.
Everywhere.
Yeah, put them in there.
Anything else?
More potions?
Okay, and then over here we're going to put stuff like that.
Let's get sold.
This one...
I want to...
Actually, hold on.
Ice mirror?
Let me quickly ask the guide about that one.
And before I sell that...
Right.
I can make a cellphone later on, right?
I guess I keep this.
Seems kind of important.
I feel like that should be an accessory.
Even though it's not an accessory.
You know what I mean?
I can't equip it, but it feels like it belongs there.
It's like everything that can...
Oh, this is not the right one.
Everything that can be combined with the tinker's workshop is like an accessory to me, you know?
That type of item.
That's how I see that.
Now you...
Will you buy this, that, and that, please?
Oh, I still have a potion there, that's okay.
Grab these.
Take the chest.
Grab this and take that chest.
And then we also need to make an ore.
Let's make an ore and construction thingy.
We need to make this longer.
It's just not enough room.
The sorting must go on.
Let's just not make an end to it before we know how much we need.
You know?
Make it open-ended.
For now.
More potions.
Let's sort first.
Potions.
And then here, materials.
For potions.
Oh, I didn't actually take those yet, that's okay.
Okay, let's make two chests here.
These chests are all temporary, by the way, the looks of them.
I'm gonna change the look to be appropriate for the item that's inside.
You know, so this would be like organics later on or something.
Because of the look, it's like bamboo.
But in here for now, we're gonna put ores.
And I guess gems belong with ores, for now.
That's... I'm not gonna separate those.
They are the same thing in my mind.
And then we also need construct... let me get rid of that.
So ores, in.
Any other ores?
Let me actually just eat this chocolate chip cookie, because I don't want it in my inventory.
Yeah, I don't know how to sort this yet.
Let's go back up.
All this.
Those are all ores, that's nice and easy.
Okay, like that, like that.
And this one, this one, this one.
Okay, not bad.
Gold ore, gold bar.
Diamonds, amber.
Cool.
That's a good start.
In fact, I don't need multiple shadow keys.
I only need one.
Whoops.
Will you buy these?
You will.
Fantastic.
Thank you.
Take all this.
Take all the fishing, because we're also gonna have a fishing chest.
Maybe the fishing chest can be combined with a food chest or something.
Maybe this can be fishing.
And stuff like that.
There we go.
Master bait, German bait, scorpion.
We can have a food chest next to it or something.
Or maybe I should just put the buff stuff next to the potions as well.
Nah, nah, let's not do that.
Let's not go too crazy here.
That is a bit too crazy.
In fact, it's unheard of.
You can't do stuff like that.
You know what's funny?
The more I sort this item, the more my mind gets sorted right now.
I feel like I'm slowly lifting a fog of confusion over my head the more I do this.
It's painful as fuck to go through this, but it's worth it.
Spikes sell it.
It's not even a material.
Yeah, I have six golden keys.
That's also kind of...
They do get consumed, right?
Or do they?
I don't think they do.
In fact, I don't remember that happening.
You can have the apple.
Honestly, you can have the chicken nuggets too.
They just take up space and I have cooked fish.
This is all construction.
This is weirdo chest.
In fact, for now...
Let's get rid of all the weirdo stuff.
Later on, I will buy it again.
For now, just get rid of it.
It's going to confuse me.
I need to keep things simple.
I need this to be as cluttered free as it possibly can get.
Stuff like the owl and shit.
You know, let's get rid of that.
The only use I have for that is to put it in a terrarium, right?
Anyway...
Actually, no, I can make a roasted bird.
Minor improvements, but it's kind of shit, right?
Let's actually cook as much as we can here.
The pot is up here.
There it is.
Fuck yeah.
I'm cooking!
This is how we consolidate.
And make everything nice.
I'll go up here.
All right, what's the rest of the fishing?
Did I take all of it?
The goldfish.
Actually, hold on.
What's the goldfish special?
Fishbowl.
Wait, what do you mean, equipable?
On my head?
Bowl of soup.
Oh, no!
Abomination.
I can make that.
Sure.
Make a couple of those.
Get rid of that.
One honey block can get destroyed.
Why is my character, like, phasing like that?
Maybe it's always been there.
That's just confused me.
I wonder if I can put a sign in the game that would say what it was that I'm looking at.
I know you can rename chests, but something that would be visible immediately.
Like Minecraft.
Maybe there's a way to do that.
Owl gets deleted.
So hold on.
This is the fishing.
This shall be the food.
Stuff like that.
And here we...
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no, no, no.
We need to put in...
that.
Huh.
Not even sure what to do with that.
Okay, do we have any more ores?
I don't think so.
Potions?
I don't think so either.
Where was material?
Here.
Material, material, material.
Nope, this belongs in the other one.
That is indeed something for potions.
So is that.
So is this, I guess.
Actually, I'm not sure.
I don't remember.
Whoa!
Losing my mind.
Delete.
This is the material.
So is that.
Let's put that there for now.
Why can I have this on me?
Huh.
All right.
All of this right here gets sold.
No thanks.
I hate these so much.
Off you go.
I do love all of these though.
And all that.
So this is potions here.
Potions was where?
Yes.
Okay, there you go.
And now in here we put all the stuff for potions.
And just like gardening, you know, things to plant and stuff like that.
I guess the vertebra is more like a material.
So is that.
This goes in here.
Actually hold on vertebra is also used in potions now.
Maybe it is.
Wait.
Mushrooms.
No, delete that.
And we have the next stage here we can put things in.
If we need it.
And then in here.
All the bait.
Just there.
Sort.
This can be construction.
Everything construction related goes in there.
Take all that.
Oh, wait a minute.
I wanted a block only chest.
So the right chest here is going to be blocks.
Yeah, something like that.
Let's put a chest there.
These are all blocks like this.
Oh, this is a wall.
Wall goes in the construction.
Oh, wrong one.
Wrong one.
Oh, that's fine.
And here we put the walls.
No, fuck.
The opposite way.
I'm an idiot.
There we go.
And this goes in here then.
The Skyward door.
Construction.
Where are these torches?
Hellforge.
Already have that.
You know what?
Let's sell these instead.
I guess we'll get something out of it.
Okay.
We have all this crap.
All that crap.
All that.
Maybe I'll have like...
Maybe I'll have a wall.
Nah, that's way too much organization there, I think.
I think it's way better to just have a chest dedicated to like decoration.
And the other one is like building, you know?
So like here I could put or like even chest there.
In here I'm going to put stuff like paintings.
Actually, they all kind of flow together, I guess.
These are materials.
Wait, did I... Oh, I already said this was construction.
Ah, wait, it's fine.
This is construction.
Yeah, they all flow together here.
That's okay.
Ah, this is ores.
This is that.
Here we go.
Maybe...
Spell to.
I
have all these things here.
Oh, no.
The better option is to dig down.
And make it a little...
Because I'm going to put all this building stuff down here.
That's what I'm doing.
Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
Much better.
This is how we're going to do it.
Wait, where do...
Do I not have any more?
Okay, better.
Then I want to put stuff like this here.
I'm just going to put it there for now.
You know?
This looks stupid as hell.
But honestly, it needs to be like this.
If you want to keep this shit organized, it's got to be the way...
It's got to be.
Pretty much.
Okay, this goes in here.
Deathweed.
Hay.
Shell pile, desert fossil.
I feel like that's construction.
Actually, this is kind of useless.
Get rid of that.
And this is a material.
Also a material, but hay is more like...
construction.
Like that.
It's a block, right?
Silt.
I can actually use that here.
And now I should be able to do this.
Nice.
The good thing is here, as soon as I get things put in these chests, later on, I will be able to click this magical button.
And hopefully, it's just going to...
sort it so beautifully.
So a thing I have to keep in mind is that whenever I want to take things out of chests, I should never take all of it.
I should always take everything except one.
So that I can always put it back.
But that's a pain in the ass to do every time.
So there's that.
But it is a strategy that I can utilize.
At least.
It seems to be a good idea in theory.
In practice though, we'll have to see.
Mushrooms.
Here.
Seems okay.
What did I just do?
Oh, I clicked on the thingy.
All right.
Grab these.
Let's throw them down over here.
Because why not?
Let's keep this shit a little bit organized.
This one is almost empty.
All the chests are gone.
Look at that.
Finally.
Paintings.
I wonder if Obsidian Workbench does something special.
Yeah, I'm not gonna sort this stuff.
This is just randomized building things.
That stays randomized.
There's no way I'm going deep over that.
Put an anvil here.
Delete that one.
Bamboo chest.
And then I also want a place for stuff like this.
The eyes and whatever.
Very, very specialized.
Items.
You know?
Such as this as well.
It's very, very special.
Those items.
Maybe that can be in these.
Let's put weird-ass items in here.
This is glass, goes in there.
Potions.
There.
Now, didn't I also have a bunch of stuff in these?
I kind of forgot about that as well.
Oh, god.
Actually, it's okay, I think.
Because...
I can click this button now.
Oh, no!
Only a little bit got...
Oh, my god.
I wish I could, from this interface, click this button.
Quick stacked nearby chests from inside one of these.
You know?
But no.
Not today.
Also, the explosive powder, I wanted to test that as well.
As well as the magma stone.
There's all these kinds of things here that I haven't tested yet.
Because they've been scattered everywhere in all the chests.
And it's been impossible to find my way around.
Get rid of all this stuff.
Cax belongs in there, I guess.
No, actually, that's more like a potion thing.
There was ore here, right?
Wait, no, this was materials.
This is also weird-ass items.
There was ore.
Here.
There.
Whoo!
My hands!
Sunplay block.
There.
Delete the detonators.
Snow block goes in here.
Skyward chest, let's put that there for now.
Delete the wooden arrows.
Or kalkem ore.
Or re-kalkem ore, get rid of that.
Now, the soul of light, I feel like that is obviously a material, yeah.
So we start the next chest.
Maybe I sort these by rarity.
The higher up you go, the rarer it is.
Something like that, maybe.
And then these were the weird-ass items.
So that means, I guess keys can go in here.
Already have a shadow key, delete that.
That's weird.
That's... get rid of that.
That's a weird item.
That's a shitty item.
And we have this one.
Up there.
Acorn.
Nah,
I don't know about acorn.
Maybe also here.
Alright, now we have these.
No, this is vanity.
Here we can put this in.
That in.
That's vanity.
Get rid of that.
Why do I get all this dirt randomly?
Where does that come from?
Vanity in here.
That is potions.
Now living fire block that goes over here because these are blocks.
Alright.
Oh, that's a potion actually.
There you go.
Alright, slowly starting to get organized here.
I guess I should just...
Instead of having sold the banners, I could have just hung them I guess.
But like I've done here.
Yeah, maybe I'll just hang the banners in here, you know.
Let's do that.
This will be the banner room.
Banner room!
Banner there as well.
So that whenever there's an invasion here, we're gonna have as many chances as possible to have a buff, you know.
And I may as well put them somewhere.
Okay, so here.
Sort.
Do we have duplicates?
Actually, we somehow don't.
That's amazing.
Isn't that amazing?
Wait, oh no.
Can they hang from a platform?
Let's test.
They can't.
Can they just hang freely?
Okay, good to know.
Whoops.
So what I want to do is like this.
And then I want to make a platform right below that.
It's that way, I can just...
put all the banners.
Oh my god, my fingers are hurting.
And that seems good.
The rest will get sold.
Okay.
Very nice.
Sell, sell.
Sell.
Awesome.
Now give me this.
Whoops.
Oh!
That's the key line for deleting.
I didn't even realize that was a key line for that.
Let's say that's the end for this building here for now.
We can always expand it later if we need to.
We also have some couple empty chests here as well for future stuff.
It's something.
Now didn't we have a door?
I'm going to use this for now.
Obsidian door, there you go.
Beautiful.
Because why not?
Okay.
Actually no.
Let's keep this consistent.
We did all this work.
Let's not falter at the finish line here.
I need woodworking.
Make one door, please.
Okay, now we need wall.
Now we need wall.
So let me see what I have.
What kind of walls I have.
I have a lot of plank wall.
That needed stone.
I can make stone wall.
How's that look?
Not too great.
I do like plank wall.
I have to remind myself what I need to make that.
Yeah, let's see here.
Plank wall needs any wood and stone block.
And then just sawmill for that.
So that's that one.
Okay.
This may actually be enough.
Actually, I'm not sure.
Maybe not.
So let's test something real quick.
If I put this on.
Here.
Yeah, it will place one further, actually.
Yes, it will.
It will be working like that.
This is like one of those times in real life where you know when you have to do the dishes.
You don't want to do the dishes.
So things end up piling up and then you do it all at once.
This is that.
And the optimal thing to do is to just clean it as soon as you use something.
Instead of letting it pile up.
So from now on, I'm going to be cleaning it as I go.
As much as I can.
Obviously, I can't guarantee that will always happen, but I'm going to do my damnedest.
To keep it clean because the game does not offer many tools to help you in that regard.
It's just like...
Yeah, we don't have any options to automatically sort or search items or any of that quality of life.
So you got to do that yourself.
Come up with something.
I want to make more wood.
Hold on a second.
So I can make more of this wall.
I think I'm missing a couple spots.
Anything?
Oh, I see a spot there.
There we go.
Keep placing.
Anything missing?
Nice.
I think we did it.
And now we can also put lights in between the chests, actually.
This is perfect.
You know, temporary, but something like this.
That way we can actually see what the hell we're doing in here.
Look at that.
Beautiful.
We need a bit more wood.
Nobody wants to live here, huh?
That's so weird because it's such an awesome place.
I just noticed, by the way, we haven't dealt with any enemies in a while.
And it's because there was no grass.
So I'm gonna go out here and fucking mow this lawn.
Everything needs to go.
That's what you need to do.
Whenever you build, mow the lawn first.
Right?
I mean, there's no grass.
Get rid of the grass.
Fuck that grass.
Okay, good.
I wonder if this grass counts down here.
Away with it.
Oh, this guy's here.
So they're spawning here.
Why are they spawning here?
Unless, hold on.
Have I been misunderstanding the grass term here?
Is this the grass?
Or is it the grass that I fell with my weapon?
Like the tall grass.
Because over here...
I mean, actually, there is grass here.
But it's not the tall grass.
So I don't know.
Weird.
Definitely need more wood.
Let's plant some trees.
I have that over here.
Oh, actually.
Oh!
Notice how it sort of automatically...
Wait.
Look, it separates them.
It really wants to put it...
Oh, wait.
Yeah, look, it really wants to put it there.
I wonder if that's the minimum distance.
Now it doesn't do it anymore.
What?
Wait a minute.
Actually, I don't know.
Huh?
It's not doing...
What the...
Huh?
What did that just change?
What?
Huh?
Wait a minute.
It's because there's no grass here?
Oops.
Fuck.
Wait a minute.
I'm so confused.
Oh, okay.
Wait a minute.
Ah, you can't place it on dirt, which is weird.
Why can't you plant a tree in the dirt?
Isn't that what you do?
Huh?
Weird.
Why are there suddenly so many enemies?
Why was I spared before?
I don't understand what I have done?
Why was I be...
Why was I able to build for so long with no enemies?
And then suddenly...
What?
I don't get it?
Oh well.
Okay, finally.
Things are starting to look clean here.
So now I should be able to click here.
Things go in.
Except...
So here's the thing, I took all the acorns.
That was a mistake!
I should have taken everything except one.
How do I do that?
Is there a keybind for taking everything except one?
I'm trying...
All the...
I mean, I guess I could do this and put one back.
But ugh!
Really?
I guess I could.
No, don't.
There we go.
Okay.
Now the... somehow enemies are here now.
I don't get it?
Is it this here, maybe?
Wait, there's a banner there.
Banner!
I already have one of those.
Get rid of it.
You can have it.
And the empty bucket is also a weird-ass item, so that goes in a weird-ass chest.
The rest here gets locked, like that.
So let's see, which one was the weirdest one?
Yep.
That's the weird-ass chest.
There.
So now, whenever I have to take something out.
Only!
Only one at a time.
Or else.
I'm gonna regret it.
That's like the trick, right?
Uh, okay.
Good.
Things are starting to look up.
We also have all this.
So let me click on this button.
Let's see how much gets sorted.
Not as much as I had hoped, but that's because we don't have all these in the right spot.
The warding dune rider boots.
They do indeed belong in these chests.
Raid of mana potion.
Uh, that one.
It's like, I want to say it belongs here.
No, actually it doesn't.
But I feel like it does, you know what I mean?
That goes in there.
Weird-ass item.
Actually, weird-ass item goes in the weird-ass chest.
This one I also want to ask about.
Actuator, delete that.
Delete that.
Okay, materials.
That one, that one, that one.
Delete.
That looks good.
And we have these two weapons here.
In.
And this one.
And potions.
Whoops, I just removed the torch.
Delete these.
Put this in here.
Silt.
There we go.
Delete the statue.
Sand goes in here.
Now we should be able to sort all this.
Nice, nice.
Very good.
These are the very rare items, things that I don't know what to do with.
You know what I mean?
Yet.
Or, I mean, I do know what to do with them, but it's not something you want to carry on you all the time.
Or whatever.
Copper or Tungsten, do I really not have them in here?
That's almost unbelievable.
Oh, I did, why didn't they get sorted?
Interesting.
That stays here as well.
There's chests, there's slimes in here.
Get out!
How dare you get in here?
There we go.
This is the most...
This is like a warehouse.
It's a weeeearehouse.
In fact, let me make the warehouse look a little nicer.
Like that.
Just smoothen those edges.
Look at that.
Add so much.
So good.
Okay.
All right, man, look how clean this fucking inventory looks.
Has this inventory ever been this clean?
Huh?
We put the money in here now?
We sort the money.
I have two platinum, dude.
Almost three platinum.
Void bag.
We still have some stuff here.
Take it.
Can we sort?
Not at all.
Water leaf seeds, they belong over here.
Somewhere.
I think.
Right?
No?
Wait.
Ah!
I removed the thingy.
Where did I put that?
Ah, here.
Titanium ore, delete this.
Prostone block.
That's vanity.
No, that's actually not vanity, but yeah.
Equitable.
In.
And then the ore.
Titanium.
Block is here.
And then this armor.
There.
My god!
This is looking mighty fine.
Give me all that.
Let me take all this crap and put it over here.
Let's put the forge next to...
the ores, huh?
Forge.
Furnace.
Let's delete one of these.
Extractinator.
Sawmill.
Let's just put it there, I guess.
Anvil.
Delete one of them.
There.
Actually, hold on.
Let's put this stuff here instead.
Anvil.
And this...
Can I stack them?
Can I put it on top of...
Just testing for optimizations here.
Lacksmith rack.
There's no room for that.
Solidifier.
Sawmill.
Actually, let's put all the stuff that is usually used the most close to each other, you know?
Something like that.
Heavy workbench.
Actually, that should be there.
There.
Sawmill.
Let's do...
Oh, the workbench.
Wait a minute, I wonder...
I don't need this one anymore, the iron.
This one will suffice.
For everything, right?
I'm pretty sure.
Last kill.
Bone welder.
Alchemy table.
That should be next to this.
Ah, but that's okay.
So, on this alchemy table...
I'm actually gonna put a little...
table next to it.
And put the little bottle on it.
I need some wood.
Come on, trees, grow!
Nice.
And then...
We make a little...
Actually...
Better idea.
This is a great idea.
Ah, wait.
Put this next to this one.
Oh, wait, is there something there?
The turtle is actually annoying me a little bit.
I can't see what's happening.
Oh.
There, and then we put the bottle on top of that.
And then we have the alchemy table right next to it.
See, that's smart.
And, optimally, I also wanna bring Maurice.
No, wait, Jeff.
I wanna bring Jeff over here and live here.
Because then I can keep asking him about combinations while I craft.
This is totally insane.
There we go.
Actually, put it to the right.
And then...
There.
Whoops.
Furnace, furnace, furnace, furnace.
Where?
Hold on.
There we go.
Ah, I didn't pick it up.
Hellforge.
The witching table.
Ah, it was this one I wanted to put.
Kill.
This may look completely insane.
It's, like, so ugly-looking.
But I don't care.
It is what it is.
This is totally...
I don't even know.
Actually, I'm gonna sell that.
The piggy bank.
Let's put that on top of this one.
See how that fits?
Oh, I can't.
Ah, crap.
Can I put this on top of anything here?
Oh, no.
But hey, we need a table and a chair anyway, right?
For...
For Big J.
Jeff, that is.
Oh, wait, I need to make that over here.
In fact, don't I already have some?
Have a table.
You get to live right here.
One chair.
There we go.
And on top of that table, we're gonna have a piggy bank.
And now, who lives here?
Jeff!
What?
Why couldn't I... is this house not...
Wait a minute.
Is there limits to the size of a house?
I guess there is, in a weird way.
All right, well.
Fine.
Okay.
I can also...
Make something nice happen here, right?
Maybe not.
Oh, the pot.
There.
See?
Ah, I fucked up already.
Leave one.
So if I go like that now...
Look at that.
That looks nice.
That's beautiful.
Very cool.
All right, man.
This is starting to look like something.
And now I need a little bit of... so I can click this now.
Why?
Wait.
Oh, is it because it's up there?
Ah, okay.
So anything that's up on this first bar does not actually get sorted.
Okay.
That's good to know.
Very good.
And I can't put this anywhere, unfortunately.
Maybe over here.
Nah.
I don't know if this actually does anything.
Maybe it's just for the looks.
Down here we can do all kinds of new things.
We have so much room for activities now.
Next to this place, I'm going to build a... either here or on the other side.
It's going to be planters.
The money in there.
The extractinator.
I would never put that here.
Ah,
shit.
Let's remove the pot.
We got to move this one over.
The extractinator.
There's just about room enough here.
Look at that.
We have to expand this, though, at some point to get room for all this.
That's okay.
It is what it is.
Oh, piggy bank.
It needs to be put back.
Oh, wait, where did I... on the table.
There we go.
And it is his house, right?
What do you mean?
There is all of this.
Huh?
Wait a minute.
What?
Did the little block...
This is going to be a terrible night.
I don't understand what's wrong with this.
There's plenty of light.
Is it because this is right next to it?
Hold on.
Fine, I'll put it...
torch.
How about now?
Okay, that... weird.
I think there's a maximum size a house can be, otherwise it bugs out.
The hell?
Alright, let me sell this.
Maurice.
The extractinator.
Did I...
So I can't put that in here.
Let me just expand a little bit.
Now.
Take all...
and leave one.
Let's build it like that.
Uh oh.
Oh, what's this now?
Duh.
Sure.
I don't even have any potions.
Cool.
That was fun.
Okay.
Thank God that's over.
Uh, put the door back.
Honestly, the bosses in this game may be the worst thing about this game.
I don't know.
I feel like...
they're just not that fun.
I like exploring and killing enemies and getting loot more.
The... I don't know.
Just... weird.
I like building.
I like chilling.
I like exploring and getting progression.
I don't like the bosses.
I really don't.
But anyway, I've been going for a shit ton of time actually.
I gotta prepare a friend that's coming over.
We gotta eat some dinner and stuff.
So that's gotta be it for now.
Thanks for watching.
Thank you for watching.
For watching me struggle.
I am very close to starting over on normal difficulty.
But I don't think I will.
Because I'm in too deep.
You know?
I'm way too deep.
So yeah.
Alright!
Actually, I don't have much time.
I actually gotta... I gotta clean my place a little bit.
Because it looks... it looks a little bit too... not clean.
Oh my god, Ludwig!
You've been a member for two months now.
You have gained a triangle with a dot inside.
Now what does that mean, I wonder?
That's simple.
Hmm...
Ludwig jumpscare.
Elavi, five euros.
Thank you.
Don't lose hope, Oliver.
We trust in you.
Well, I'm not gonna.
I mean, I'm gonna complain like a little child, of course, but...
I mean, I've been through fucking... what's the game called?
Rainworld.
Rainworld is punishing, but in a different way, right?
I feel like I'm slowly getting to learn all the ways of the pain.
And all the games.
Man, you guys are suggesting some hard games.
Fuck!
How about you suggest something like... The Sims next time, huh?
How about you suggest something that...
Where I can excel and where I can actually look strong, you know?
Where I will appear cool.
But I think what I've done today...
Organizing my chests...
And building for the future...
It's gonna help me immensely next time and onwards.
I think this is a turning point for the organizational part of the game.
Hopefully.
And things will get easier and I can focus more on the things that I... think are fun.
You know?
So I think I've done something great today.
It was a worthwhile investment.
Anyway, guys, thank you so much for watching on this beautiful Saturday.
The weather is actually incredible here.
I don't know about you guys.
You're everywhere in the world, so maybe it's not even the same for you.
At least in Europe right now, great weather.
I'll see you around!
Have a good weekend!
And I'm gonna be throwing up the inscription video tonight, of course.
So look forward to that one.
I've been having a blast with that game, by the way.
Borderline addicted.
So yeah, I'll see you around.
Bye-bye!